Guide to the George Mason University photograph collection, 1950s-2007
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 9: Creative Services, 1964-2007; (80 boxes)
  - Subseries 2: Chronological, 1981-2007
    - 1992-1993, November 24, 1992-January 25, 1993 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      Pablo Dominguez, Harold Geller, Randall Edwards, John Schreck; Dr. Marilyn Mobley, Human Resources employee of the month; VEBI, Southwest Virginia consortium meeting (removed); Chuck James; Duke Perry; Ron Sinacore; Statues in Mason courtyard; New VEBI board member, psychology department graphs, Human Resources employee of the month; Grant presentation; GMU vs. ODU basketball; Dr. Toni Travis, Dr. Benson Cooke; GMU and medical science research institute signing ceremony, Human Resources employee of the month; Summer school catalog; Jennie Best and her gift to GMU library "Video of the 20th Century"; GMU vs. American University; Dr. Lovett's farewell presentation and reception
    - 1993, January 27-February 7, 1993 (Box 95, Folder 4)
      Robert Weiler, Peter Brunett, Laura Massie, Joe Wood, Mick Ellis; Law School conference honoring Judge Posner; Martin Luther King Day celebration; Media Center tour for SWVA group; Monica neighbors; GMU vs. JMU mens basketball; Marjorie Haley, Wayne Gable, Lester McMenamin, Mary Hamon; Mobil 1 track meet
    - 1993, February 9-March 15, 1993 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      Human Resources employee of the month, Dr. Chery Bartholomew; Annual VEBI meeting in Richmond (removed); Mark Crain (economics); Reception for shared research instrument facility and attitude; Art Center statue, Edward Villella dance workshop, EV portrait; Physical Plant employee of the month, statue construction of "Attitude"; Dedication of sculpture "Attitude"; Portrait Mike Kelly, bronze sculpture "Three Ladies"; IDO computer demonstration; Physical Plant employee of the month secretary of the Year, Virginia McCaslin
    - 1993, March 23-April 12, 1993 (Box 95, Folder 6)
      Group shot of 1993 University employees of the month, Terry Whisnant, College Path Walk; William Rifkin and copy shots of Judge Renquist; Rhonda Wilbon, Mary Montebelle; Distinguished faculty and 25 year employees; arm wrestler Dave Patton; Evan Anderson, Mary Montebello, David Shum, recycling center, Law School reception; Copy work University Center; Hambdessa Tso (Ethiopian speaker), Human Resources employee of the month; Dr. Walker, Louis Poller; Paul Westhead press conference, Don Lavoie and John O'Connor; University Day, secretary of the year presentation; International Week; Mason Scholars, Cherrytree reception, campus statues
    - 1993, April 13-June 3, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      Physically challenged students' new parking deck; GMU vs. UMBC, student services, group shot for student HB; Dedication of gym to J. Linn, Howard Baetjer alternative energy program; GMU alumni awards brunch; PAGE program group shot, Science & Technology virtual reality demonstration; Group shot student HB, award presentation, Donna Null; Human Resources employee of the month, Physical Plant employee of the month; Edwards ground breaking; Anthropology class study in Fairfax cemetery, portrait of Dean Bafundo; GSE convocation; GMU commencement; Mason Scholars, "So to Speak" art work; Martin Marietta computer equipment gift
    - 1993, June 4-July 13, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      Library stacks project, Human Resources employee of the month; campus demolition, Krasnow conference; NVI reception; UCIS photo illustration; VA Business magazine ad; employee of the month; Paul Westhead basketball camp; golf tournament; graffiti
    - 1993, July 20-August 30, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      Campus construction of the Johnson Center; Physical Plant employee of the month, Donna Null; Margaret Andino, Pat Story; Jim Fonseca, Peter Denning; GMU Child Development Center; Dr. Gallaher - Writing Institute; Summer School catalog; Daniel Eesley PAGE student; Charlene Hurt, Elizabeth Littlefield; Pat Kendrick volleyball coach, graffiti project; Brian Drummond, SA display, Rick Davis, Tom Horan, chesnut tree; Prince William County display, Coach Paul Westhead; Dan Burke and Francesco Parisi GMU law professors; Students moving in Presidents Park, Physical Plant employee of the month; first day back in classes, registration
    - 1993, August 31-September 22, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      SBA small business development class, Johnson Center construction, Human Resources employee of the month; black student weekend brochure; Board of Directors, SA display, Ron Sinacore; Lester E. McMenamin, GMU campus; GMU students on campus; Mason, Presidential Scholars talent show, psychology graphs; Judicial Committee Group shot, Patricia Miller; Santiago Hispanic Heritage month; C. K. Williams, Susan Tidry, Peter Klappert, all authors; Fiction writers G. W. display; Garden Club presentation; PAGE reunion; J. Dyke speaking at GMU Law School
    - 1993, September 23-October 15, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      Edward James Olmos program and reception; Governor Doug Wilder's press conference to University Presidents; Arts Gala jewelry; Dean Mendes, University Center construction; Raymond Akwule, Human Resources employee of the month Terry Ashton; Basketball training, Karen Crouch scholarship recipient; Bridgit McElroy, African American print design, Physical Plant employee of the month; Rose Pascarell and Christine Donofrio, Arts Gala jewelry; Laura Nelson, GMU students on campus playing chess
    - 1993, October 20-November 1, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      Energy Awareness and Conservation Day, Jim Fletcher, soccer; Rose Pasarell, GMU campus; Nicole West, Alan Jackson in concert; Reception for the Chinese Economic delegation; Chief Justice of VA, Deborah Boehm-Davis; "Attitude" in studio set up; Eward Wegman, GMU day care kids trick or treating; Nursing awards, Chinese Cool Industry delegation
    - 1993, November 3-15, 1993 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      Pearl Wang, GMU collegiate health and fitness tour; GMU students studying in Fenwick library; Professor Mark Spikel and Herma Williams, Vicki Balenger, Mary Ann Lecos; Sargent Barnes with students, students in Fenwick, ARC awards; Harry Wechsler, AFC awards; Dance student and instructor; Karla Hoffman operation research and engineering; GMU Gala; Captain Martha Hughes-Reese, students and buildings, Black History week, composit poster
    - 1993, November 16-December 2 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      Walter Williams; GMU students in Fenwick Library and Writing Center; panel discussion with President George Johnson, Dr. Toni Travis; Health science signing ceremony with U.S. Forest Service, construction; Fred Schock, Anita Taylor, Womens Studies Advisory Group; employee of the month, GMU Jazz Ensemble, Century Club reception; GMU / NOVA student group
    - 1993-1994, December 3, 1993-January 6, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      Book signing, reception, research grant workshop; GMU Foundation group shot, construction update; Dean Sage, Dr. Conti, Dr. Butler, Dr. Johnson-Brown, Johnson Center construction; Concert Hall, Anita Taylor, Nursing and Health Science group; Dr. Nancy Laird, Dr. Doreen Harper; Johnson Center construction update, Dean Sage; Johnson Center construction update, final attachment
    - 1994, January 13-February 23, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      Ice skating program, Human Resources employee of the month; Board of Visitors meeting, construction update; April Young, employee of the month at Physical Plant; Snow, students on campus, students at library; Community policing; President George Johnson and students at construction Science & Technology, employee of the month; Danzalta display, Connie Kirkland, construction update; copy work Danzalta Parrots; VEBI meeting in Richmond; Gerontology brochure shot at Birmingham Green Nursing Home; Dr. Willett portrait
    - 1994, February 25-March 16, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      Students on campus, Physical Plant employee of the month, GMU Law School and Manhattan Institute lunch; Dom Arciszewski, construction update; copy work - Gerald Baliles, employee of the month, commencement speaker; Lovey Hamill, Joe Kanyan, Ed Codell Walter Barrett, copy work; MLK celebration, essay winners with President George Johnson, Esther Elstun, Zlata Filipovich; Julie Janoski, Bob Karlson, John Soder; Gunston Ledger, Broadside archival copy work; Ann Caderro
    - 1994, March 17-April 5, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      Physical Plant employee of the month, Bruce O'Rourke, copy work; GMU display, Chinese pictures on exhibit, Peggy Browse, Ann Field; Board of Visitors reception and coop agreement between PWCO and GM students on campus; Samuel Phillips, PAGE; Jay Shaffer and Don Gallahr; Gustavo Mellander, Lorraine Brown; Map of Virginia and Maryland, tech with media station; Dave Johnson with President George Johnson plus flag, Law School conference; Tech Link; ICAR group shot, Andrew Acland, Armen Yetegaren, Michele Duryea, H. Tuso; employee of the month, students on campus
    - 1994, April 7-May 5, 1994 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      University Day, Secretary of the Year; University Day, Concert Hall and University Center and Mason Hall, Science & Technology, Lynch lecture, students on campus; Dean Mellander, campus with students; Multi Ethnic students in group; Jim Trefil, Pat Story, Don Kelso; Students in Fenwick Library; employee of the month Raul Rivera-Murga campus buildings; Mason and Presidential Scholars, Co-op research and development agreement with Army; Law School program, Science & Technology award presentation; Oakview School, Mason Day; Conference forging strategic alliance for tech transfer; Institute of Public Policy annual spring training conference campus buildings
    - 1994, May 5, 1994 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      Prospectus
    - 1994, May 6, 1994 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - 1994, May 9-June 6, 1994 (Box 98, Folder 4)
      Governor Allen on campus; Sec. Sgro touring construction of Science & Technology with students; T.V. studio GMU; GMU commencement; Ken Bumgardner, student in computer lab; Foundation award winner technology fair; GMU T.V. station; Downtown Fairfax award luncheon; Prince William Board of Visitors; VEBI board meeting, portrait Michael Tentnowski (removed); GMU T.V. station
    - 1994, June 11-20, 1994 (Box 98, Folder 5)
      Classes of 1968-1971 reunion and reunion display; Perspectus graduate testimonials; Redi program; students on campus
    - 1994, June 23-August 1, 1994 (Box 98, Folder 6)
      Scott Smith, Physical Plant employee of the month; Students on campus and students in art class; Toni Travis; Students on campus during summer session; Norm Kerr's retirement party; Car transfer to CAEPS; CADD Microsystems, Inc.; UCIS brochure; Students on campus in summer, Physical Plant employee of the month; Physically challenged student leader Betina Greco; Writing program group shot, minority student class; Dr. Borocus and Dr. Hershy, nurses in action; University Center; Jack Kvancz farewell, GMU T.V. studio, Mary Lazarsky, Orsolya Berty, Mark Johnson and staff (writing program)
    - 1994, August 8-28, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      Joseph Shirk, University Center abstract; Mary Lazarsky, GMU T.V. studio; Mike Miller, University Center Librarian, University Center; Stephen Brown and employee of the month; GMU students and winner of NSF fellowship; UUSA retreat; Engineering open house, CFA, copy work fall season; Law School orientation, CFA, copy work, ROTC officer Lee Affen, graph; Jacqulyn Dodson, students on campus, copy work; Fall orientation
    - 1994, August 29-October 4, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 2)
      Removal of Federal Theatre Project archives; students on campus Fine Arts faculty show Nureim and Harry Campbell; German orphan home fund reception; business consultants library, PAGE portraits, employee of the month; Students on campus; employee of the month, Lawrence Levine, Valery Sofer, students on campus; GMU Law School mentor meeting; dance class, Russian physicians, Jacques Derrida lecture series; Gayatri Spivac lecture series, Keith Segeson and Russian physicians; Dean Fulner(?) check presentation, Dr. Johnson and GM Bank, students on campus; Crystal vase and violin, Gala still life, campus life; Patriot's Day; Campus life; Americorps reception, campus life
    - 1994, September 12, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 3)
      Music recruitment brochure, Rick Davis, Linda Marvel; Campus life, metacomputing press conference; Luncheon information session; Campus life; Susan Slader teaching computer class, press conference new athletic director
    - 1994, October 4-October 14, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - 1994, October 15-November 8, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 5)
      Homecoming; ROTC clean up, Gala china, Mason Day; Physical Plant employee of the month, students in biology class, Kevin McCrohan; Anna Borgeryd Astuatsaturou, Nolhsbitter, Trump, ICAR; David Swanson; Lloyd DeBoer, trick or treat; Margar Kendal-Hull, University Center, Physical Plant employee of the month; Sanjeer Dewan, Chung Ki Min, Catherine McCormick, Constance Pattee, Eliz Demulder, Laura Adamkewicz, trick or treat; Rosemary Bortel, Ann Moore, Physically challenged students; Judy Allen's dance class; Lou Miller, Jim Fonseca
    - 1994, November 9-December 7, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 6)
      Dr. Holisky, Tony Maiello, Joseph Shink, Flo Graham, Venture rep, Gala, Law School mentors reception; Campus life, computers, Gala; Child development center read out, Debora Bohn Davis; Toni Morrison symposium; art classrooms, J. Clapsaddle (printing), S. Anholt (painting); Chesapeake Bay; biology class, employee of the month, students on campus; Field House restoration, student studying
    - 1994-1995, December 10, 1994-January 13, 1995 (Box 99, Folder 7)
      Dr. Radner's English class, non fiction writing class; Campus life, students study, students with computers, library; Joyce Williams (Nursing), Major Jim Fullbrook; Evelyn Slaght (Nursing); Ellen Dawson (Nursing), Bethany Hall-Long (Nursing); Dr. Joseph Gurfine, Dr. Christopher Hill; Science & Technology II presentation; Ruth Zambrana; employee of the month, University Center construction; Copy work Donald Hall, Richard Bausch, CK Williams, Carolyn Forche, Robert Bly, Jim Fletcher, Sondra Patrick; Physical Plant employee of the month; University Center
    - 1995, January 16-February 4, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      Larry Bowens, Enterprise Hall; Admissions, registration; Mr. Ghandi; Community services fair; IET meeting, Raymond Cypress, students on campus; Law School, Judge Kozinske co-teaching with Jeff Parker and D. Bruce Johnson; Julian Bond, snow, students, library; snow, students on campus
    - 1995, February 6-11, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      Snow, students on campus; Students on campus, Vincent Desnoes, Nancy Woolover, employee of the month; Jane Cushman; Wrestling (color prints); Choral department
    - 1995, February 14-20, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 3)
      Snow, students on campus, Lisa Major, Miss Black Virginia; Snow on campus, chemistry class; Men's basketball vs. JMU; Alumni affairs "Pizza", admissions interviews by alumni; Keith Bushey, students in library, students on campus
    - 1995, February 21, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      Mobil track meet,
      contact sheets, negatives, color photographs
    - 1995, February 21, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 5)
      Mobil track meet, color photographs
      prints
    - 1995, February 22-March 15, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 6)
      Admissions, student gallery; Science & Technology check presentation apprentice photo workshop, students on campus; Alumni affairs awards committee, Phon-A-Thon fund raiser, Cynthia McIntyre; University day care, students on campus, protocol agreement; GMU women alumni; employee of the month; Mary Silva copy work, Kevin Clements copy work; Science & Technology; Copy work, year book, Dr. Clark's English class; Professor Ashcraft's sculpture class, computer art, publications staff; Crew club
      negatives, black and white photographs
    - 1995, March 21-31, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 7)
      Lynn Fontana, Dulce Cruz, science lab; Art department, office moves, Science & Technology; Father Bob Celinski, office moves, campus buildings, student at computer; Awards luncheon, Wayne Froman, copy work, chemistry class; Karen Rosenblum, Heather McDonald; 25 year employees, students on campus; Tech Link; Margaret Hanson winner of customer service award, sculpture class; GMU crew team
    - 1995, April 3-19, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 8)
      Lynch lecture, Ghandi; International Week; employee of the month group, Herma Williams; Baseball, Mason vs. Liberty; Alternative spring break; International Week; Science & Technology awards luncheon, Mason Week; John Wallin, Nursing School, blood pressure testing; International Week, GM student teacher library; University Day; Jenna Van Hook, Greek Week; John Sennett, student bias brochure; Bias brochure, Buss Grover (student)
    - 1995, April 19-May 5, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 1)
      Check presentation from Cantina Del Rio, campus buildings, Fenwick Library; New Century College, Mason scholars with President George Johnson; Mason Day aerial photos, graphs for chemistry department; Alumni affairs awards with Susan Rook; Til Hazel receiving award, employee of the month Shirley Nathan; copy work, Stan Harrison, Til Hazel; sculpture, Law School economic analysis
    - 1995, April 26-July 5, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 2)
      Edwin Lynch, Kiosk SUB 1; graduation; John Sennett Bais brochure enterprise building; Kenneth A. Kovach, students on campus, employee of the month
    - 1995, May 7-July 14, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 3)
      Music reception with donors Foundation Check Presentation; laser in Science & Technology: Retirement party for Dr. J. Palmer, stage combat class; Weird science (color); BAIS brochure, Donna Bufundo; graduation with David Potter, Stanley Harrison, Lynn Bauer, Mary Sprewl with Rector; Saudi students, nursing coordination; Science & Technology award presentation, Foundation luncheon Mrs. Johnson and Mrs. Dahia, Board of Visitors; employee of the month Nellie McCoy, employee of the month Claudia E. Young, Mason Scholars (copy work); Students on campus; Mason Scholars, copy work; Fairfax City; PWI color transparencies; Bob Smith, Lauve Steenhuisen; Mark Spikell, Camp Mason, recycling; Camp Mason, Sports Camp; Students, flowers, lake, NEBI student group, Dennis Webster
    - 1995, July 14-27, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 4)
      Arts Academy summer party final show; VEBI meeting (removed); VEBI, Greg Guagnon, Keith Bushy, Linda Westphal, Paul D'Andrea; David Miller, John O'Connor, Karen Oates, Ce Ce Rodgers, Matthew Cozad; Ed Fleishman group, Maury Sherrens, Fred Rossini, Duke Perry; Psychology charts; Campus restaurants, bookstore, workmen on campus; Judge Leslie Alden, Diane Turner; John O'Connor, Mark Spikell, Daniel Druckman; Lawrence Butler, Thun Luc, Physical Plant employee of the month; Larry Van Wert, Miguel Gonzales, Susan Trencher, Saudi nurses; Edwin Lynch, Kiosk SUB 1
    - 1995, August 2-21, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 5)
      David Potter, Linda Seligman, Sandra McDowel employee of the month, John O'Connor, PWI Rec. agreement; Linda Westphal, Keith Bushey, Sondra Patrick, Sheila Folliott; Optical device, Gazette; Duke Perry, Maurice Sherrens, Fred Rossini; University Center interior; PTAP variable signs; campus construction, League of Women Voters of Fairfax; Alumni recruters, New Century, Esther Elstun scholarship to German orphans
    - 1995, August 28-September 16, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 6)
      Registration, students on campus; New Century College, biology class (pond), bookstore; PAGE freshman class, group shot, students on campus; Greg Guagnano; George Ansivino, students in Enterprise Hall; Daris Berg - employee of the month, Major donor to Foundation; Alan Cheuse English department; PWI bround breaking; George Mason (copy work), Physical Plant employee of the month, Physical Plant construction; William H. Lawrence
    - 1995, September 19-October 5, 1995 (Box 101, Folder 7)
      National Hispanic heritage Month opening ceremony; First EIP graduates at Board of Visitors meeting, Heritage professors, Dick Bausch, Stephen Burton; Gala committee members; students on campus, Gala committee members; Physical Plant employee of the month Jose Vasquez; Fenwick Library, dining hall, Enterprise Hall with students; Diversity Center with students; Students on campus, University Center construction
    - 1995, October 6-17, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 1)
      Harry Wechsler, employee of the month Leslie McKenney (Executive Secretary Legal Affairs); Ann H. Cary (Nursing Professor); Hortensia Cadenas, PAGE group; Roy Rosenzweig, students on campus; Karen Cohn, Janet Niblock, Frank Hoben; Patriot's Day, Carol Mattusch, Priscilla Regan; Jonathan Grifford, Roger Stough, Mark Maggio, Brien Benson, Kingsley Haynes, Frank Hoban, Karen Cohn, group, Janet Niblock, group; Richard J. Klimoski (Psychology), Joel Forman, Kitty Hover and staff, Enterprise Hall
    - 1995, October 18-November 27, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 2)
      Mary Lou Crouch with students; New Century College, Pond Project; Library learning center information; Physical Plant employee of the month, Graham Waldo; Biology class, Toni Morrison, students in learning center, ROTC, students on campus; Enterprise Hall, Krug, Robinson lecture, Thompson, SUB II, Science & Technology I and II; Menas Kafatos Professor Physics and Astronomy; GMU Gala, GM Bank grand opening, Amy Erwin; Brett Wright, Elly Doyle; Physical Plant employee of the month Glenda L. Weston; Jean Sorrell
    - 1995-1996, November 29, 1995-January 18, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 3)
      Physical Plant employee of the month Mike Kelly; Mary Silva, graduate MBA class, high tech distance learning; University Center; Ann Carey, "Jenny" Chien-Yun Wu; Ronnie Feeg, Rita Ailinger; Promised practises, TIPP, D. Anderson, Gail Milgram, BJ McConnely; Foundation check presentation; Art Saunders; Science & Technology scholarship presentation, Physical Plant employee of the month Kenton Gordon; Richard Ruberstein, Dennis Sandole; employee of the month Luanne Pearce; mail services employees Pat Lindsey; Michelle LeBaron, Frank Blechman, Kevin Clements; Catherine (Cass) Connelly; Graduation 1985, President George Johnson in hard hat
    - 1996, January 24-February 15, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 4)
      Learning center, registration, bookstore; Dr. Johnson with Heritage chair, Peter Burnette (English department); Teri Franceschi, natural gas truck; Lisa Page (English department); Martin Luther King celebration; Physical Plant employee of the month Pete Crisman; Crowd at basketball game (color negatives); Learning center; Cyrus Cassells opera workshop; cat coalition, employee of the month, U.S. Forsetry, Geoffrey Birchard, Human Resources; Basketball
    - 1996, February 18-28, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 5)
      Campus snow scene, Johnson Center; Learning center, bookstore, library; Housing welcome; Physical Plant employee of the month David Wilder; GMU Foundation Phone-A-Thon; Job fair, Mary Wakefield, Senate Building, Senator Russell Feingold, Jeff Bingaman; African American Studies reception for Gilbert Morris with Dr. Potter and Dr. Mobley
    - 1996, February 29-March 19, 1996 (Box 102, Folder 6)
      EIP reception award to President George Johnson; GMU job fair; Presidential search Martha Gilliland; Donaldson GMU Presidential candidate; Agnes Mao, employee of the month, Michael Kelly, Martha Gilliland; Presidential candidate Victorio Aguera; William Martin (Education); William Martin (GSE); Eugenie Mielczsnek, Alan Merten; James Trefil (Physics); Emmett Holman (Philosophy and Religion); Charter signing between U.S. Forest Service and GMU; Peter Henriques, Walter Moretz
    - 1996, March 20-April 12, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 1)